<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quantized Complex Crypto</title>
    <link>https://qcc.fangsong.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Quantized Complex Crypto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://qcc.fangsong.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum-secure Pseudorandom Permutations</title>
      <link>https://qcc.fangsong.info/2017-06-quantumprp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qcc.fangsong.info/2017-06-quantumprp/</guid>
      <description>This is a long due note concerning constructing quantum-secure pseudorandom permutations (QPRP), a problem that has made my collaborators (Andrew Childs, Shih-Han Hung, Zhengfeng Ji) and myself excited as well as disappointed a couple of times over the past few years. In a way this makes it a perfect fit for the debut post of this blog.
A while ago, Mark Zhandry observed in a note that some existing constructions are immediately quantum-secure for simple reasons, hence confirming the existence of QPRPs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://qcc.fangsong.info/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qcc.fangsong.info/about/</guid>
      <description>Quantized Complex Crypto Entangled Thoughts on Quantum Computing, Cryptography, and TCS broadly!  Quantized Complex Crypto was a blog name that Fang Song came up with not long after he started his PhD journey. He scribbled a word or two then, but they didn&amp;rsquo;t go anywhere, unfortunately. A few years later, he decided to give it a second chance. Don&amp;rsquo;t be disappointed should it not go far, again!
Fang Song is a theoretical computer scientist, working on exciting subjects that some day people will truly care.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>